<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chinwei: Design Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://chinwei.me/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chinwei: Design Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://chinwei.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Divvy</title>
      <link>http://chinwei.me/works/divvy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chinwei.me/works/divvy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Divvy&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;The fastest way to split bills at the table&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
	&lt;video class=&#34;mobile&#34; autoplay loop controls poster=&#39;/assets/divvy-poster.jpg&#39;&gt;  
	   &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/divvy.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio:2)&#39;&gt; 
	  &lt;!--  &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/splitbill/splitbill.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-webkit-max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (max--moz-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-o-max-device-pixel-ratio:1)&#39;&gt;  --&gt;
	&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
    Divvy-ing meal bills is much quicker without having to deal with names. Prototype built and recorded with Adobe XD.    
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;Divvy is a quick, no frills way of splitting bills with friends at the table. Just enter the price of each item and decide who to split it with. Instead of typing the name of your friends, assign them each an animal for the duration of the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;It is an idea I an toying with during my free time. It came about when I came across similar situations and thought there should be a quick and straightforward way to handle it.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;h3&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;I currently like that the entire flow is contained within one view, and at this point it seems to be efficient for certain cases. At the moment I like the ideas of using animals to reference people. They can be easily made attractive while being neutral and effective as long as they are visually distinct. It could also potentially be fun, given the context, to address your friends using animals. 🐔🐼🐙🐳&lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;p&gt;One issue that should be considered is that currently the flow revolves around itemization, which works well for smaller number of items. For larger bills it would probably be more efficient to start with the total amount and isolate items that are not equally split.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;Another point to be looked into is identifying the situations where the host is expected to split the bill equally (or not). In some cases it is obvious, for instance, if a vegetarian participates in a (meat heavy) barbeque, my understanding of social norms tell me that the participants should not expect the vegetarian to pay for the meat. Aside from this, there are many other situations in which it is not as obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;This is an ongoing personal project that I am planning to build as I learn Swift. Check back for future iterations!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;




</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pensieve</title>
      <link>http://chinwei.me/works/pensieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chinwei.me/works/pensieve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Pensieve&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;Write notes and associate them with your contacts&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
	&lt;video class=&#34;mobile&#34; autoplay controls loop poster=&#34;/assets/pensieve-poster.jpg&#34;&gt;  
	   &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/pensieve.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio:2)&#39;&gt; 
	  &lt;!--  &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/splitbill/splitbill.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-webkit-max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (max--moz-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-o-max-device-pixel-ratio:1)&#39;&gt;  --&gt;
	&lt;/video&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
    A messaging flow should be familiar to many people. Here I am exploring to see whether it makes sense to repurpose the flow to reference people instead. Built using Sketch and Framer.  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;Pensieve is a place where you can write notes and associate them with people. When you take a note, it captures the date and location to help you better recall the ideas that has to do with a context and person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;

	&lt;video controls autoplay loop&gt;  
	   &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/pensieve-gomix.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio:2)&#39;&gt; 
	  &lt;!--  &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://chinwei.me/assets/splitbill/splitbill.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-webkit-max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (max--moz-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-o-max-device-pixel-ratio:1)&#39;&gt;  --&gt;
	&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
	    Video prototypes can only get me so far. This prototype allowed me to test out the interaction on my phone. Built the app logic in Gomix, used Twilio for handling SMSes and Firebase for storage.
	&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;



&lt;p&gt;With Pensieve, you can record pieces of information about during informal interactions and because your notes live on a timeline, it is easy to look back at the notes and thoughts you recorded relating to a person. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, you may have discussed an idea during coffee break with a colleague. Or if you&#39;re working on a project for a client, you can use it to take note of important details, like when you expect a document, without having to create and name a document using apps like Google Docs or Evernote for each entry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPMC</title>
      <link>http://chinwei.me/works/mychoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chinwei.me/works/mychoice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;MyChoice&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;Extending healthcare beyond hospital walls&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/mychoice1%402x.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Note: Due to a NDA with UPMC, I cannot reveal our findings or end solution. Here, I will focus mostly on our process.&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;h3&gt;Improve patient engagement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a culmination of Carnegie Mellon’s Master’s of HCI program, this 8-month project was sponsored by the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC) to look into a patient-facing tool with the goals of deeper engagement with the health system and better health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;h3&gt;Approach&lt;/h3&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the project, we conducted user research, ideated, refined and iterated our designs until we arrived at a high fidelity solution that was validated by our users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/mychoice2%402x.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;Diary studies and home visits gave us an intimate understanding of the challenges that hypertension patients deal with day-to-day which ultimately helped us design a better solution&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the research phase of the project, we studied patient lives, behavior change strategies, spoke with clinicians, and developed key insights which informed our ideas toward this goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/mychoice3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following that, we validated our ideas with our users, by getting them to interact with prototypes of increasing fidelity. At the end of the prototyping phase, we built a mobile app prototype using PhoneGap and Cordova that could track the location of our users.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;About UPMC&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC) is an integrated global non-profit health enterprise that has more than 62,000 employees, 22 hospitals, and a 2.2 million-member health insurance division. They are also ranked one of top ten hospitals in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fluigdata</title>
      <link>http://chinwei.me/works/fluigdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chinwei.me/works/fluigdata/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
	&lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Fluig Data&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;An end-to-end data exploration platform&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/fluigdata-1.jpg&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;In Fluig Data, data from multiple sources are mapped to Data Models, like the Customer Data Model shown here. Rules are then set up to protect the resulting Golden records from low quality data.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;

	&lt;h3&gt;About Fluig Data&lt;/h3&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;Enterprises need clean data to generate and track business metrics, but many of them tend to have business units that generate and store partial information of the same entity in siloed systems, leading to duplicate and inconsistent information. Fluig Data addresses this by centralizing all information about an entity into a Data Model, then applying rules to reject, duplicate and transform incoming data to produce a reliable single source of truth which is then used to generate insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/fluigdata-2.jpg&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;After the records are processed, a dashboard gives an overview of the outcome&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;http://chinwei.me/assets/fluigdata-3.jpg&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;The mobile companion app allows various teams within the company to access key information about customers and other companies&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;constrain-width half-width margin-auto&#34;&gt;

	&lt;h3&gt;Involvement&lt;/h3&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;As part of a team of about 15, and as one of two UX designers, I have been broadly involved in the development of Fluig Data from the beginning and in various capacities. My contributions have been mostly in the area of designing the user interface, flows and interactions, conducting interviews and usability studies, but I have touched on several other areas as well.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;Some highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;ul&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;I initiated and conducted the first user research activities in the company, including interviews and usability studies.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;Before we had a dedicated UI engineer, I built the UI on top of our framework (Angular Material at that time) and later built custom components to better flows specific to our product.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;After the release of Invision Craft&#39;s nested symbols, I re-created the UI components used in the product and centralized them using Invision Library to sync them across multiple documents and make them accessible to the team.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;I defined a standard for task specifications so that the team can have a shared understanding of the information they needed before they began working on a task.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;I convinced the team to switch over to Trello from JIRA because I wanted to make it easier and faster to create and get information about development stories.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;For a significant portion of the development, I conducted sprint planning, retrospectives and prioritized stories. Having visbility over user needs and business goals helped guide many of my decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>