<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works-rsses on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works-rsses on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Divvy</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/divvy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/divvy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Divvy&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;The fastest way to split bills at the table&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;video controls&gt;  
   &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/assets/divvy.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio:2)&#39;&gt; 
  &lt;!--  &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/assets/splitbill/splitbill.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-webkit-max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (max--moz-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-o-max-device-pixel-ratio:1)&#39;&gt;  --&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Divvy is a quick, no frills way of splitting bills with friends at the table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No need to get all your friends to sign up for an account just so you can split a bill. Divvy works on the device, so it is always quickly accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skip the naming. Mentally associate an animal to each friend you are chilling out with (temporarily!) for a more streamlined and enjoyable flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an ongoing personal project that I am doing for fun. Do reach out if you would like to provide feedback, or want to help out!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pensieve</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/pensieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/pensieve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Pensieve&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;Write notes and associate them with your contacts&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;video autoplay controls&gt;  
   &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/assets/pensieve.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio:2), (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio:2), (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio:2)&#39;&gt; 
  &lt;!--  &lt;source type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; src=&#39;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/assets/splitbill/splitbill.mp4&#39; media=&#39;(max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-webkit-max-device-pixel-ratio:1), (max--moz-device-pixel-ratio:1), (-o-max-device-pixel-ratio:1)&#39;&gt;  --&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pensieve is a place where you can write notes and associate them with people. When you take a note, it captures the date and location to help you better recall the ideas that has to do with a context and person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Pensieve, you can record pieces of information during informal interactions, like an idea during coffee break with a colleague. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re working on a project for a client, you can use it to take note of important things, like when you expect a document, without having to create and name a document on Google Drive for each interaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because your notes live on a timeline, it is super easy to look back at the notes and thoughts relating to a person.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPMC</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/mychoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/mychoice/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;MyChoice&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;Extending healthcare beyond hospital walls&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note: Due to a NDA with UPMC, I cannot reveal our findings or end solution. Here, I will focus mostly on our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;improve-patient-engagement&#34;&gt;Improve patient engagement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a culmination of Carnegie Mellon’s Master’s of HCI program, this 8-month project was sponsored by the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC) to look into a patient-facing tool with the goals of deeper engagement with the health system and better health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;approach&#34;&gt;Approach&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the project, we conducted user research, design, and development of a high fidelity technology solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We studied patient lives, behavior change strategies, spoke with clinicians, and developed key insights and visions toward this goal. Our numerous design visions were refined to one idea, which we developed into a mobile app prototype and concept video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the user experience lead, I played a key role in designing and building the various prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-upmc&#34;&gt;About UPMC&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC) is an integrated global non-profit health enterprise that has more than 62,000 employees, 22 hospitals, and a 2.2 million-member health insurance division. They are also ranked one of top ten hospitals in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fluigdata</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/fluigdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 15:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/works/fluigdata/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;div class=&#34;article-header&#34;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;title&#34;&gt;Fluig Data&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&#34;byline&#34;&gt;An end-to-end data exploration platform&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-in-silos&#34;&gt;Data in Silos&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Large enterprises use multiple software to store different parts of information about people, products and other entities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these software are not interconnected which makes assembling a complete picture difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;explore&#34;&gt;Explore&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluig Data allows analysts, operational staff and business leaders in an organization to access information about their customers and products on demand and generate dashboards to track performance metrics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-quality&#34;&gt;Data Quality&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having clean, accurate data is a prerequisite to having meaningful and actionable insights. Fluig Data makes it easy to onboard data sources via connectors to internal and public data sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It structures, normalizes, cleanses and validates the data to create a reliable source of truth for an record.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>